<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<root>
    <doclet-version-NOT-library-version>1.00</doclet-version-NOT-library-version>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListByte</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListByte</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getAsString">getAsString</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList as a String.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList and converts it to a String. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index as a String. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance of type T as a String.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index as a String, or a default-constructed instance of type T as a String if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="addAll">addAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds all items from an array to this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds all items from the specified array to this ArrayList. If the size type of this ArrayList is DYNAMIC and
 * the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList, it resizes this ArrayList to accommodate the new items.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array does not exceed the capacity of this ArrayList, it adds the items from the array to this ArrayList.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList and its size type is STATIC, it prints an error message and does not add the items.
 *
 * @param other The array/List whose items should be added to this ArrayList.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were added successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Byte[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insertAll">insertAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts all items from an array at a specific index in this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts all items from the specified array at the specified index in this ArrayList.
 * If the index is greater than the count of items in this ArrayList, it returns false.
 * If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the items from the array at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the items.
 * @param other The array whose items should be inserted.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Byte[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="toArray">toArray</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Converts the ArrayList to an array.
 *
 * This function copies the items from the ArrayList into the specified output array.
 * The output array must be large enough to hold all items in the ArrayList.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param outputArray The array into which to copy the items.
 * @return The output array.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Byte[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="subtoArray">subtoArray</name>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Byte[]</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function sets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @param type The size type to set.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @return The size type of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListInt</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListInt</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getAsString">getAsString</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList as a String.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList and converts it to a String. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index as a String. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance of type T as a String.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index as a String, or a default-constructed instance of type T as a String if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="addAll">addAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds all items from an array to this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds all items from the specified array to this ArrayList. If the size type of this ArrayList is DYNAMIC and
 * the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList, it resizes this ArrayList to accommodate the new items.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array does not exceed the capacity of this ArrayList, it adds the items from the array to this ArrayList.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList and its size type is STATIC, it prints an error message and does not add the items.
 *
 * @param other The array/List whose items should be added to this ArrayList.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were added successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Int[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insertAll">insertAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts all items from an array at a specific index in this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts all items from the specified array at the specified index in this ArrayList.
 * If the index is greater than the count of items in this ArrayList, it returns false.
 * If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the items from the array at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the items.
 * @param other The array whose items should be inserted.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Int[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="toArray">toArray</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Converts the ArrayList to an array.
 *
 * This function copies the items from the ArrayList into the specified output array.
 * The output array must be large enough to hold all items in the ArrayList.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param outputArray The array into which to copy the items.
 * @return The output array.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Int[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="subtoArray">subtoArray</name>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Int[]</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function sets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @param type The size type to set.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @return The size type of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListUInt</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListUInt</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getAsString">getAsString</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList as a String.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList and converts it to a String. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index as a String. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance of type T as a String.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index as a String, or a default-constructed instance of type T as a String if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="addAll">addAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds all items from an array to this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds all items from the specified array to this ArrayList. If the size type of this ArrayList is DYNAMIC and
 * the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList, it resizes this ArrayList to accommodate the new items.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array does not exceed the capacity of this ArrayList, it adds the items from the array to this ArrayList.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList and its size type is STATIC, it prints an error message and does not add the items.
 *
 * @param other The array/List whose items should be added to this ArrayList.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were added successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>UInt[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insertAll">insertAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts all items from an array at a specific index in this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts all items from the specified array at the specified index in this ArrayList.
 * If the index is greater than the count of items in this ArrayList, it returns false.
 * If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the items from the array at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the items.
 * @param other The array whose items should be inserted.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>UInt[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="toArray">toArray</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Converts the ArrayList to an array.
 *
 * This function copies the items from the ArrayList into the specified output array.
 * The output array must be large enough to hold all items in the ArrayList.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param outputArray The array into which to copy the items.
 * @return The output array.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>UInt[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="subtoArray">subtoArray</name>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>UInt[]</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function sets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @param type The size type to set.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @return The size type of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListLong</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListLong</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Long</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Long</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Long</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Long</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getAsString">getAsString</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList as a String.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList and converts it to a String. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index as a String. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance of type T as a String.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index as a String, or a default-constructed instance of type T as a String if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Long</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Long</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Long</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="addAll">addAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds all items from an array to this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds all items from the specified array to this ArrayList. If the size type of this ArrayList is DYNAMIC and
 * the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList, it resizes this ArrayList to accommodate the new items.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array does not exceed the capacity of this ArrayList, it adds the items from the array to this ArrayList.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList and its size type is STATIC, it prints an error message and does not add the items.
 *
 * @param other The array/List whose items should be added to this ArrayList.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were added successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Long[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insertAll">insertAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts all items from an array at a specific index in this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts all items from the specified array at the specified index in this ArrayList.
 * If the index is greater than the count of items in this ArrayList, it returns false.
 * If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the items from the array at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the items.
 * @param other The array whose items should be inserted.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Long[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="toArray">toArray</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Converts the ArrayList to an array.
 *
 * This function copies the items from the ArrayList into the specified output array.
 * The output array must be large enough to hold all items in the ArrayList.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param outputArray The array into which to copy the items.
 * @return The output array.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Long[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="subtoArray">subtoArray</name>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Long[]</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function sets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @param type The size type to set.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @return The size type of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListULong</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListULong</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>ULong</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>ULong</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>ULong</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>ULong</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getAsString">getAsString</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList as a String.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList and converts it to a String. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index as a String. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance of type T as a String.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index as a String, or a default-constructed instance of type T as a String if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>ULong</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>ULong</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>ULong</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="addAll">addAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds all items from an array to this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds all items from the specified array to this ArrayList. If the size type of this ArrayList is DYNAMIC and
 * the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList, it resizes this ArrayList to accommodate the new items.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array does not exceed the capacity of this ArrayList, it adds the items from the array to this ArrayList.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList and its size type is STATIC, it prints an error message and does not add the items.
 *
 * @param other The array/List whose items should be added to this ArrayList.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were added successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>ULong[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insertAll">insertAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts all items from an array at a specific index in this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts all items from the specified array at the specified index in this ArrayList.
 * If the index is greater than the count of items in this ArrayList, it returns false.
 * If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the items from the array at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the items.
 * @param other The array whose items should be inserted.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>ULong[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="toArray">toArray</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Converts the ArrayList to an array.
 *
 * This function copies the items from the ArrayList into the specified output array.
 * The output array must be large enough to hold all items in the ArrayList.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param outputArray The array into which to copy the items.
 * @return The output array.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>ULong[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="subtoArray">subtoArray</name>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>ULong[]</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function sets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @param type The size type to set.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @return The size type of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListDouble</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListDouble</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Double</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Double</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Double</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Double</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getAsString">getAsString</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList as a String.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList and converts it to a String. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index as a String. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance of type T as a String.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index as a String, or a default-constructed instance of type T as a String if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Double</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Double</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>Double</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="addAll">addAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds all items from an array to this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds all items from the specified array to this ArrayList. If the size type of this ArrayList is DYNAMIC and
 * the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList, it resizes this ArrayList to accommodate the new items.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array does not exceed the capacity of this ArrayList, it adds the items from the array to this ArrayList.
 * If the total count of items in the ArrayList and the array exceeds the capacity of this ArrayList and its size type is STATIC, it prints an error message and does not add the items.
 *
 * @param other The array/List whose items should be added to this ArrayList.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were added successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Double[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insertAll">insertAll</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts all items from an array at a specific index in this ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts all items from the specified array at the specified index in this ArrayList.
 * If the index is greater than the count of items in this ArrayList, it returns false.
 * If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the items from the array at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the items.
 * @param other The array whose items should be inserted.
 * @param length The length of the array/List.
 * @return true if the items were inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>other</name>
                <type>Double[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="toArray">toArray</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Converts the ArrayList to an array.
 *
 * This function copies the items from the ArrayList into the specified output array.
 * The output array must be large enough to hold all items in the ArrayList.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param outputArray The array into which to copy the items.
 * @return The output array.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Double[]</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="subtoArray">subtoArray</name>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>outputArray</name>
                <type>Double[]</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function sets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @param type The size type to set.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)
 *
 * @return The size type of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <class>
        <name>B4R::B4RArrayListString</name>
        <shortname>ArrayListString</shortname>

        <method>
            <name DesignerName="Initialize">Initialize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Constructs a new ArrayList.
 *
 * This constructor creates a new ArrayList with the specified size type, initial size.
 * The size type determines whether the size of the ArrayList is static or dynamic. The initial size specifies
 * the initial capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * @param type The size type of the ArrayList. This should be either DYNAMIC or STATIC.
 * @param initialSize The initial capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>initialSize</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="add">add</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Adds an item to the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function adds the specified item to the ArrayList. If the size type of the ArrayList is DYNAMIC and the ArrayList is full,
 * it resizes the ArrayList to accommodate the new item. If the ArrayList is not full, it adds the item to the ArrayList.
 * If the ArrayList is full and its size type is STATIC, it does not add the item.
 * @param item The item to add to the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="insert">insert</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Inserts an item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function inserts the specified item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is greater than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns false. If the ArrayList is full, it resizes the ArrayList if its size type is DYNAMIC, or returns false if its size type is STATIC.
 * If the index is valid and the ArrayList is not full, or has been resized successfully, it shifts all items from the index to the end of the ArrayList one position to the right, inserts the item at the index, and increments the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to insert the item.
 * @param item The item to insert.
 * @return true if the item was inserted successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeItem">removeItem</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the specified item from the ArrayList. If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it prints an error message and returns false.
 * If the item is found in the ArrayList, it removes the item from the ArrayList and returns true.
 *
 * @param item The item to remove from the ArrayList.
 * @return true if the item was removed successfully, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="remove">remove</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes an item at a specific index from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes the item at the specified index from the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it shifts all items from the index + 1 to the end of the ArrayList one position to the left, and decrements the count of items.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to remove.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="clear">clear</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Clears all items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function clears all items from the ArrayList and sets the count of items to 0.
</comment>
            <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="get">get</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function retrieves the item at the specified index in the ArrayList. If the index is less than the count of items in the ArrayList,
 * it returns the item at the index. If the index is out of bounds, it returns a default-constructed instance.
 *
 * @param index The index of the item to retrieve.
 * @return The item at the specified index, or a default-constructed instance if the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::B4RString*</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="contains">contains</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList contains an item.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList contains the specified item. If the item is found in the ArrayList, it returns true.
 * If the item is not found in the ArrayList, it returns false.
 *
 * @param item The item to check for.
 * @return true if the ArrayList contains the item, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="indexOf">indexOf</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Finds the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the index of the first occurrence of the specified item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
 * It iterates over the ArrayList from the beginning to the end, comparing each item with the specified item using the == operator.
 * If it finds a match, it returns the index of the match. If it does not find a match, it prints an error message (if debug is true) and returns -1.
 *
 * @param item The item to find in the ArrayList.
 * @return The index of the first occurrence of the item in the ArrayList, or -1 if the ArrayList does not contain the item.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Int</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="capacity">capacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the capacity of the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current capacity of the ArrayList, which is the maximum number of items it can hold without resizing.
 *
 * @return The capacity of the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="size">size</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Retrieves the count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function returns the current count of items in the ArrayList.
 *
 * @return The count of items in the ArrayList.
</comment>
                 <returntype>UInt</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="isEmpty">isEmpty</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Checks if the ArrayList is empty.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList is empty. If the ArrayList is empty, it returns true. If the ArrayList is not empty, it returns false.
 *
 * @return true if the ArrayList is empty, false otherwise.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="set">set</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Sets the item at a specific index in the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function updates the item at the specified index in the ArrayList with the provided item.
 * If the index is within bounds, it sets the item and returns true if the operation succeeds.
 * If the index is out of bounds, it returns false.
 *
 * @param index The index at which to set the item.
 * @param item The item to set at the specified index.
 * @return true if the item was successfully set, false if the item was not set or the index is out of bounds.
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="removeRange">removeRange</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Removes a range of items from the ArrayList.
 *
 * This function removes a range of items from the ArrayList, from the specified fromIndex (inclusive) to the specified toIndex (exclusive).
 * If fromIndex is greater than toIndex, or if either index is out of bounds, it prints an error message and returns without removing any items.
 * If the indices are valid, it shifts all items from toIndex to the end of the ArrayList to the left to fill the gaps left by the removed items, and decrements the count of items by the number of removed items.
 *
 * @param fromIndex The start index of the range to remove (inclusive).
 * @param toIndex The end index of the range to remove (exclusive).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>fromIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>toIndex</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="ensureCapacity">ensureCapacity</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Ensures that the ArrayList can hold at least the specified number of items without needing to resize.
 *
 * This function checks if the ArrayList's current capacity is less than the specified minimum capacity.
 * If it is, it resizes the ArrayList to the specified minimum capacity.
 * The function uses the memcpy function to copy the items to the new array, so the type T must be trivially copyable.
 *
 * @param minCapacity The minimum capacity that the ArrayList should be able to hold without resizing.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>minCapacity</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="trimToSize">trimToSize</name>
<comment>
 * @brief Trims the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size.
 *
 * This function reduces the capacity of the ArrayList to its current size, i.e., the number of items it contains.
 * If the ArrayList is dynamic and its capacity is greater than its size, it creates a new array with a capacity equal to the size, copies the items to the new array, and deletes the old array.
 * If the ArrayList is already trimmed or is fixed size, it prints an error message (if debug is true).
</comment>
                 <returntype>Bool</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="concat">concat</name>
<comment>
 * @brief add String from item(index2) to String in item(index1).
 *
 * This function dont change ArrayList size.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index1</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>index2</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="join">join</name>
<comment>
 * @brief add B4RString to String in item(index1).
 *
 * This function dont change ArrayList size.
</comment>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>index1</name>
                <type>UInt</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>item</name>
                <type>B4R::B4RString*</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="setSizeType">setSizeType</name>
                 <returntype>B4R::void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>typeSize</name>
                <type>Byte</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name DesignerName="getSizeType">getSizeType</name>
<comment>
*
 @brief Gets the size type of the ArrayList.

 This function gets the size type of the ArrayList. (DYNAMIC, DYNAMIC2, FIXED)

 @return The size type of the ArrayList.
/
</comment>
                 <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </method>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_FIXED">B4R_FIXED</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
<comment>
ArrayType
</comment>
        <field>
            <name DefineMethod="true" DesignerName="LIST_DYNAMIC">B4R_DYNAMIC2</name>
            <returntype>Byte</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <version>1</version>
</root>