<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <doclet-version-NOT-library-version>1.07</doclet-version-NOT-library-version>
    <class>
        <name>igolub.googleapiavailability.b4a.GoogleApiAvailabilityWrapper</name>
        <shortname>GoogleApiAvailability</shortname>
        <comment>IMPORTANT! Add next line to manifest:
&lt;code&gt;AddApplicationText(&lt;meta-data android:name="com.google.android.gms.version" android:value="@integer/google_play_services_version" /&gt;)&lt;/code&gt;</comment>
        <owner>process</owner>
        <event>OnMakeGooglePlayServicesAvailableResult (Available As Boolean)</event>
        <method>
            <name>ShowErrorNotification</name>
            <comment>Displays a notification for an error code returned from IsGooglePlayServicesAvailable2, if it is resolvable by the user.</comment>
            <returntype>void</returntype>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name>CheckAndMakeGooglePlayServicesAvailable</name>
            <comment>Checks and attempts to make Google Play services available on this device if it is not available. Event OnMakeGooglePlayServicesAvailableResult will be fired when fixing procedure is finished by user or if fixing procedure is not required.
EventName: name of event to be fired.
ShowInfoDialog: True to show dialog which displays a localized message about the error and upon user confirmation (by tapping on dialog) will direct them to the Play Store if Google Play services is out of date or missing, or to system settings if Google Play services is disabled on the device. False to start solution activity without showing error dialog.</comment>
            <returntype>void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>ba</name>
                <type>anywheresoftware.b4a.BA</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>EventName</name>
                <type>java.lang.String</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>ShowInfoDialog</name>
                <type>boolean</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <method>
            <name>MakeGooglePlayServicesAvailable</name>
            <comment>Attempts to make Google Play services available on this device if it is not available. Event OnMakeGooglePlayServicesAvailableResult will be fired when fixing procedure is finished by user or if fixing procedure is not required.
EventName: name of event to be fired.
ShowInfoDialog: True to show dialog which displays a localized message about the error and upon user confirmation (by tapping on dialog) will direct them to the Play Store if Google Play services is out of date or missing, or to system settings if Google Play services is disabled on the device. False to start solution activity without showing error dialog.
ConnectionResult: integer value returned by IsGooglePlayServicesAvailable2 call. If it is equal CONNECTION_RESULT_SUCCESS then OnMakeGooglePlayServicesAvailableResult event will be fired immediately with True result.</comment>
            <returntype>void</returntype>
            <parameter>
                <name>ba</name>
                <type>anywheresoftware.b4a.BA</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>EventName</name>
                <type>java.lang.String</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>ShowInfoDialog</name>
                <type>boolean</type>
            </parameter>
            <parameter>
                <name>ConnectionResult</name>
                <type>int</type>
            </parameter>
        </method>
        <property>
            <name>GooglePlayServicesUpdateIntent</name>
            <returntype>anywheresoftware.b4a.objects.IntentWrapper</returntype>
            <comment>Returns Google Play Services install or update intent.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>ErrorResolutionIntent</name>
            <returntype>anywheresoftware.b4a.objects.IntentWrapper</returntype>
            <comment>Returns the intent which will direct the user to either the Play Store if Google Play services is out of date or missing, or system settings if Google Play services is disabled on the device.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>IsPlayStorePossiblyUpdating</name>
            <returntype>boolean</returntype>
            <comment>Returns True if Google Play Store can be updated and if a new version exists. Otherwise False.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>IsUserResolvableError</name>
            <returntype>boolean</returntype>
            <comment>Returns True whether an error can be resolved via user action or if Google Play Services are available.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>GooglePlayServicesPackageName</name>
            <returntype>java.lang.String</returntype>
            <comment>Returns package name for Google Play services.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>GooglePlayStorePackageName</name>
            <returntype>java.lang.String</returntype>
            <comment>Returns package name for Google Play Store application.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>GooglePlayServicesVersionCode</name>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
            <comment>Returns Google Play services client library version code.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>GooglePlayServicesSettingsIntent</name>
            <returntype>anywheresoftware.b4a.objects.IntentWrapper</returntype>
            <comment>Returns Google Play Services settings intent.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>IsGooglePlayServicesAvailable</name>
            <returntype>boolean</returntype>
            <comment>Returns True if Google Play services is installed and enabled on this device, and if the version installed on this device is no older than the one required by this client. Otherwise returns False.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>IsGooglePlayServicesAvailable2</name>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
            <comment>Verifies that Google Play services is installed and enabled on this device, and that the version installed on this device is no older than the one required by this client.
Returns one of following int values: CONNECTION_RESULT_SUCCESS, CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_MISSING, CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_UPDATING, CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_VERSION_UPDATE_REQUIRED, CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_DISABLED and CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_INVALID.</comment>
        </property>
        <property>
            <name>IsPlayServicesPossiblyUpdating</name>
            <returntype>boolean</returntype>
            <comment>Returns True if Google Play Service can be updated and if a new version exists. Otherwise False.</comment>
        </property>
        <field>
            <name>CONNECTION_RESULT_SUCCESS</name>
            <comment>The connection was successful and Google Play Services are available.
Constant Value: 0</comment>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
        </field>
        <field>
            <name>CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_VERSION_UPDATE_REQUIRED</name>
            <comment>The installed version of Google Play services is out of date. This is an user resolvable error.
Constant Value: 2</comment>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
        </field>
        <field>
            <name>CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_UPDATING</name>
            <comment>Google Play service is currently being updated on this device. This is not an user resolvable error but error dialog will be shown if you call MakeGooglePlayServicesAvailable with ShowInfoDialog=True.
Constant Value: 18</comment>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
        </field>
        <field>
            <name>CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_MISSING</name>
            <comment>Google Play services is missing on this device. This is an user resolvable error.
Constant Value: 1</comment>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
        </field>
        <field>
            <name>CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_DISABLED</name>
            <comment>The installed version of Google Play services has been disabled on this device. This is an user resolvable error.
Constant Value: 3</comment>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
        </field>
        <field>
            <name>CONNECTION_RESULT_SERVICE_INVALID</name>
            <comment>The version of the Google Play services installed on this device is not authentic. This is not an user resolvable error but error dialog will be shown if you call MakeGooglePlayServicesAvailable with ShowInfoDialog=True.
Constant Value: 9</comment>
            <returntype>int</returntype>
        </field>
    </class>
    <version>1.0</version>
    <author>Ivica Golubovic</author>
    <dependsOn>com.google.android.gms:play-services-base</dependsOn>
</root>
